Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1778-1999 (Box 136-538)
  - Part B, 1948-1999 (Box 291-538)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1972
    - International Management and Development Institute, 1971
    - Interreligious Peace Colloquium, 1973-1979, (5 folders)
    - Israel
      - 1987-1990, (6 folders)
      - 1991, (3 folders) (Box 417)
    - Jaffee Center for Strategic Studies, University of Tel Aviv, Israel, reports, 1989, (2 folders)
    - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1968-1970
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America (Box 418)
      - Board of Directors meetings, 1977-1979, (4 folders)
      - Board of Overseers meetings, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
      - Bylaws, 1974-1975, undated
      - Correspondence
        - 1969-1971, (3 folders)
        - 1972-1977, (13 folders) (Box 419)
        - 1978-1991, (9 folders) (Box 420)
      - Printed matter, 1973
      - “Response of Jews to Crisis,” transcript of study group, 1970-1974, (2 folders)
    - Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, Md. (Box 421)
      - Arbitration proceedings with Morgan Stanley & Co., 1987
      - Board of Trustees meetings
        - 1974, Jan-1978, May, (7 folders)
        - 1978, June-1987, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 422)
        - 1987, Oct.-1989, Jan., (9 folders) (Box 423)
        - 1989, Feb.-1991, Jan., (8 folders) (Box 424)
        - 1991, Feb.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 425)
      - Commencement address by Linowitz, 1990, May 24
      - Committee on Tenure, 1978-1979
      - General correspondence
        - 1973-1981, (9 folders)
        - 1982-1991, (10 folders) (Box 426)
      - Peabody Institute, Advisory Council
        - Clippings, 1989-1990
        - Correspondence
          - 1986
          - 1987-1990, (4 folders) (Box 427)
        - Governor's Task Force on Peabody Institute, 1989
        - Meetings, 1986-1989, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1989, undated
      - Presidents
        - Candidate search, 1989-1990, undated
        - Muller, Steven, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 428)
        - Richardson, William C., 1990
      - School of Advanced International Studies, Advisory Council
        - Canadian Embassy Building Task Force, 1987-1989
        - Central American and Caribbean Program, 1982-1984, (5 folders)
        - Correspondence
          - 1969-1980, (4 folders)
          - 1981-1990, (6 folders) (Box 429)
        - Gulf War Study Group, 1991, (3 folders)
        - Latin American Studies Program, 1988
        - Meetings
          - 1969-1978, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 430)
          - 1987-1990, (7 folders)
      - South Africa, 1985-1987
      - Task Force on Finance and Governance, 1988-1989, (3 folders)
    - Jundi Shapur University, Ahvaz, Iran, Advisory Board (Box 431)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1972
      - Reports, 1969-1972, (2 folders)
    - Kennedy Center Productions, 1973-1980, (3 folders)
    - Krents, Milton E., 1968-1974, (2 folders)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under Law
      - 1966-1972, (2 folders)
      - 1975-1989, (4 folders) (Box 432)
    - Literacy Volunteers of America, 1987-1988
    - Mainstream, Inc., 1975-1978
    - Marine Midland Banks, Buffalo, N.Y.
      - Acquisitions Committee, 1972-1974
      - Board of Directors meetings, 1974
      - Correspondence
        - 1973, Oct.-1974, July
        - 1974, Aug.-1977, Mar., (5 folders) (Box 433)
      - Miscellany, 1974, (2 folders)
    - Maurer, Fleisher, Zon & Associates, Washington, D.C., 1971-1974
    - Meridian House Foundation, 1969-1973, (2 folders)
    - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, Washington, D.C., 1977-1978
    - Mexico, 1976-1979
    - Mutual Life Insurance Co. of New York, Board of Trustees (Box 434)
      - AIDS Task Force Report, 1986
      - Correspondence
        - 1970-1982, (13 folders)
        - 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 435)
      - Meetings
        - 1974, Mar.-1978, Sept., (6 folders)
        - 1978, Oct.-1979, Dec., (5 folders) (Box 436)
        - 1991, June-Aug.
      - Member lists, 1970-1974
      - Miscellany, 1974-1979 (Box 437)
      - Nominating Committee, 1982-1983
    - National Academy for Public Policy, proposed, 1981
    - National Academy of Sciences
      - Correspondence
        - 1982-1990, (9 folders)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 438)
      - President's Circle, transcripts of meetings, 1991, (2 folders)
    - National Alliance of Business
      - 1974, Mar.-1979, Sept., (7 folders)
      - 1979, Oct.-1987, Oct., (6 folders) (Box 439)
    - National Board on Graduate Education
      - 1971, Aug.-1972, May, (3 folders)
      - 1972, June-1973, Mar., (6 folders) (Box 440)
      - 1973, Apr.-Oct., (6 folders) (Box 441)
      - 1973, Nov.-1974, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 442)
      - 1974, Oct.-1975, undated, (6 folders) (Box 443)
    - National Book Committee, 1970-1971, (3 folders)
    - National Commission on Coping with Interdependence, 1974-1975 (Box 444)
    - National Executive Service Corps, 1987-1990, (4 folders)
    - National Humanities Center, 1974-1980, (6 folders)
    - National Institute of Social Sciences
      - 1968-1971
      - 1972-1974 (Box 445)
    - National Planning Association, 1971-1977, (5 folders)
    - National Urban Coalition
      - Alternative federal budget for fiscal year 1974, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - Chairmanship, 1970-1971
          - A-Br, (2 folders)
          - Bu-K, (13 folders) (Box 446)
          - L-Y, (10 folders) (Box 447)
        - Post-chairmanship
          - 1971
          - 1973-1981, (14 folders) (Box 448)
          - 1982-1992, (2 folders) (Box 449)
      - Counterbudget: A Blueprint for Changing National Priorities, 1971-1972, (3 folders)
      - Economic conditions, 1974, undated
      - Gardner, John William (1912-2002), speeches
        - 1968-1969, (3 folders)
        - 1970 (Box 450)
      - Holman, M. Carl, 1970-1971, 1988
      - Miscellany, 1970-1971, 1978, (3 folders)
      - National priorities statement, 1970-1971, undated, (3 folders)
      - Notes, undated
      - Speeches and writings file
        - 1968-1969
        - 1970-1974, (10 folders) (Box 451)
        - Undated, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 452)
      - Steering Committee
        - 1977, Aug.-1978, Mar., (4 folders)
        - 1978, Apr.-1979, Feb., (7 folders) (Box 453)
        - 1979, Mar.-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 454)
      - Urban homesteading, 1972-1974, undated, (5 folders)
      - Washington Research Project, Washington, D.C., 1970
    - New Directions, Washington, D.C., 1976-1977
    - New York state
      - Chancellor's Panel on University Purposes, State University of New York
        - Correspondence, 1970, (3 folders)
        - Reports and printed matter, 1967-1970, undated, (5 folders) (Box 455)
      - Task Force on Financing Higher Education
        - Clippings, 1972-1973
        - Correspondence, 1972-1973
        - Meetings and related material
          - 1971, Feb.-1972, Nov., (3 folders)
          - 1972, Dec.-1973, Apr., undated, (5 folders) (Box 456)
        - Reports, 1972-1973, (2 folders)
        - Staff memoranda, 1973, undated, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 457)
      - Temporary State Commission on the Future of Postsecondary Education in New York State, 1976-1977, (3 folders)
    - New York State Bar Association, 1966-1971, (4 folders)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1968-1973, undated (Box 458)
    - Norton Simon Inc., Foundation Commission on the Business-Government Relationship, 1972-1974
    - Pan American Airways Corp.
      - Annual reports, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
      - Board of Directors meetings
        - 1978, Jan-Nov., (5 folders)
        - 1978, Dec.-1979, Dec., (5 folders) (Box 459)
      - China, 1979
      - Clippings, 1972, 1978-1979, undated
      - Corporate marketing plan
        - 1979
        - 1980, (3 folders) (Box 460)
      - Corporate plan, 1978-1979, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1975, Mar.-1977, Dec., (2 folders)
        - 1978, Jan.-1983, Mar., (12 folders) (Box 461)
        - 1983, Apr.-1984, Nov., (5 folders) (Box 462)
      - Financial reports
        - 1978, (3 folders)
        - 1979, (4 folders) (Box 463)
      - International Advisory Board
        - Correspondence, 1978-1979
        - Meetings
          - 1978, Apr. 3
          - 1978, Oct. 4, (1 folder) (Box 464)
        - Miscellany, 1978, undated
      - International air transportation negotiation policies, 1978
      - Miscellany, 1977-1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Monthly performance reports
        - 1978, Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - 1978, Mar.-Aug., (6 folders) (Box 465)
        - 1978, Sept.-1979, Mar., (6 folders) (Box 466)
        - 1979, Apr.-Sept, (6 folders) (Box 467)
        - 1979, Oct. (Box 468)
      - National Airlines acquisition and merger case
        - “Clipper” (newsletter), 1978-1979
        - Clippings, 1978-1979, undated
        - Exhibits, 1978, undated
          - Vol. 1
          - Vol. 2, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 469)
          - Vol. 3, (4 folders)
          - Vol. 4, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 470, Box 471)
          - Vols. 5-6, (6 folders)
        - Legal briefs, 1978-1979, (5 folders) (Box 472)
        - Miscellany, 1978-1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Newsletters
        - “A. M., News Briefing for Top Management from Public Relations,” 1978-1979
        - “Notes from Headquarters... and around the World,” 1978-1979, (5 folders) (Box 473)
      - Nominating Committee, 1981-1984
      - Passenger marketing plan, 1978 (Box 474)
      - Policy manual (“Red Book”), 1979
      - Political action program, 1978
      - Project authorization summaries
        - 1977, Nov.-1979, Mar., (5 folders)
        - 1979, May-Nov., undated, (2 folders) (Box 475)
      - Public Policy Committee, 1977-1979
      - Seawell, William T., speeches, 1978-1979
      - Transatlantic route proceedings, 1978
    - Pan American Development Foundation
      - 1969, May-1970, Mar., (2 folders)
      - 1970, Apr.-1973, Nov., (7 folders) (Box 476)
      - 1974, Jan.-1978, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 477)
    - Panel on Foreign Investment in Latin America, Medellin, Columbia, 1969-1970, (3 folders)
    - People's Corps, proposed, 1966-1967
    - Phi Beta Kappa Associates, 1974-1986
    - Phillips Collection, Washington, D.C., 1980-1982
    - Political campaigns
      - Carter, Jimmy
        - Correspondence, 1968, 1976-1977, undated
        - Miscellany
          - 1974-1975
          - 1976-1977, (3 folders) (Box 478)
        - Secretary of commerce, position declined, 1979, undated
      - Clinton, Bill
        - Miscellany, 1991-1993, (7 folders)
        - Perot, H. Ross, open letter to, 1992, undated (Box 479)
      - Dukakis, Michael S., 1987-1988, (2 folders)
      - Humphrey, Hubert H. (1911-1978), 1966-1968, undated
      - McGovern, George S., 1970-1972, (3 folders)
      - Mondale, Walter F., 1974, 1980-1985, undated, (6 folders) (Box 480)
      - Muskie, Edmund S.
        - Correspondence, personal, 1969-1972
        - Correspondence
          - Senior Advisory Group, 1970-1972, undated
          - Staff
            - 1970, Mar.-1971, Dec., (3 folders)
            - 1972, Jan.-July, undated (Box 481)
          - Wilson, Joseph C. (1909-1971), 1971
        - Press releases, 1970-1972, undated, (3 folders)
        - Speeches and position papers, 1970-1980, undated, (5 folders)
    - Presidential Commission on World Hunger (Box 482)
      - Correspondence
        - 1979, June-1980, Aug., (7 folders)
        - 1980, Sept.-1981, Oct., undated, (2 folders) (Box 483)
      - Full commission meeting, 1980, Jan. 18
      - Miscellaneous commission documents, 1979-1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1980, (2 folders)
      - Report
        - 1979
        - 1980, undated, (2 folders) (Box 484)
      - Technical papers, 1980
    - President's Commission on White House Fellows, 1976-1979, (3 folders)
    - Public Agenda Foundation
      - 1976-1978, (3 folders)
      - 1979-1991, (4 folders) (Box 485)
    - Publishers, 1966-1972, (2 folders)
    - Ralph Bunche Institute on the United Nations, 1974-1976, undated
    - Reading Is Fundamental, Inc.
      - 1968-1970
      - 1971-1974, (4 folders) (Box 486)
    - Right to Read program, Health, Education, and Welfare Department, 1969-1970
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., report on Latin America, 1969, undated
    - Royal Society of Arts, London, England, 1969-1973
    - Salk Institute for Biological Studies
      - Annual reports, 1970-1974, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 487)
      - Board of Trustees
        - 1969, Feb.-1972, Aug., (6 folders)
        - 1972, Sept.-1978, Dec., undated, (6 folders) (Box 488)
      - Bylaws, 1969
      - Certain-teed-Jonas Salk Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 489)
      - Correspondence
        - 1966-1974, (10 folders)
        - 1975-1984, (4 folders) (Box 490)
      - Miscellaneous reports, 1971-1974, (3 folders)
      - Plan for biological studies, 1967
      - “Program of Action,” 1967-1968, (1 folder) (Box 491)
      - Research activities, 1970-1973, (2 folders)
      - Seminar on cultural influences on American life, 1972
    - Smithsonian Luncheon Group, Washington, D.C., 1970-1974
    - Special Committee on Campus Tensions
      - Background articles, 1965-1970, 1980
      - Campus reports and opinions, 1968-1969, undated, (6 folders); (2 folders) (Box 492, Box 493)
      - Clippings, 1962, 1969-1970, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1969, May-1970, May, (6 folders)
        - 1970, June-1971, Apr., undated, (2 folders) (Box 494)
      - Final report and drafts, 1969-1970, (3 folders)
      - Meetings and related material
        - 1969, Feb.-Aug., (2 folders)
        - 1969, Sept.-1970, June, (7 folders) (Box 495)
        - 1970, July-Oct., undated (Box 496)
      - Members, undated
      - Notes, undated
      - Related reports, 1969-1970, (4 folders)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks II
      - 1978, Apr.-1979, Aug., (3 folders)
      - 1979, Oct., undated (Box 497)
    - Supreme Court Historical Society, 1975-1990, undated, (4 folders)
    - Survey Committee II
      - 1973-1974, (4 folders)
      - 1975, undated (Box 498)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1974-1977, undated, (5 folders)
    - Telephone messages
      - 1969-1974, (7 folders)
      - 1975-1980, (10 folders) (Box 499)
      - 1981-1985, (9 folders) (Box 500)
      - 1987
        - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
        - April-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 501)
      - 1991-1992, (11 folders)
      - 1998, (2 folders) (Box 502)
    - Time, Inc.
      - Africa and Middle East Newstour, 1978
      - Annual reports, 1967-1971, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
      - Audit Committee, 1971, 1978-1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Board of Directors meetings
        - 1971
        - 1972, (5 folders) (Box 503)
        - 1974-1978, (5 folders) (Box 504)
        - 1979
          - Apr.
          - June-Oct. (Box 505)
      - Budgets, 1970-1979, (4 folders)
      - Cable television
        - 1977
        - 1978, 1985, undated, (2 folders) (Box 506)
      - Conference on Antitrust, Washington, D.C., 1978-1979
      - Conference on Taxation, Washington, D.C., 1978
      - Correspondence
        - 1969-1970, (5 folders)
        - 1971-1979, 1987-1990, (13 folders) (Box 507)
      - Five-year plan review, 1978
      - Miscellany (Box 508)
        - 1965-1978, (7 folders)
        - 1979 (Box 509)
      - Nominating Committee, 1978
      - Organization of Time, Inc., and its principal subsidiaries, 1979
      - People Weekly, prototype issue, 1973
      - Photographs, 1974
      - Planning and Policy Committee, 1978
      - Preliminary two-year plan, 1972
      - Securities and Exchange Commission filings, drafts and proofs
        - 1977
        - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 510)
    - Travel file
      - 1970
        - Feb., London, England
        - June, Colombia
        - Oct., Japan, (2 folders)
      - 1971, June, Mexico
      - 1975
        - Jan., Middle East
          - Background material, (4 folders)
          - Correspondence, (3 folders) (Box 511)
          - Photographs
          - Rabin, Yitzhak, (2 folders)
          - Writings, reports, and clippings, (3 folders)
        - May, Bellagio, Italy, (3 folders)
        - Sept., Iran (Box 512)
          - Arrangements, (2 folders)
          - Correspondence
          - Writings by symposium participants, (6 folders)
        - Oct.-Nov., London, England
      - 1976
        - Feb.-Mar., South Africa, (2 folders)
        - Apr., Japan, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 513)
      - 1978, Mar., Africa and Middle East
        - Arrangements See also Oversize, (3 folders)
        - Background material, (3 folders)
        - Photographs
          - Bound
          - Unbound, (2 folders) (Box 514)
        - Reports and transcripts
          - Africa, (3 folders)
          - Middle East, (3 folders)
        - Writings and notes by Linowitz
      - 1979
        - Apr., China
          - Arrangements
          - Background material, (1 folder) (Box 515)
      - 1981, Oct., Eastern Europe and Middle East
        - Commemorative album
        - Writings and notes by Linowitz, (3 folders)
      - 1982, Jan., Egypt and Israel
        - Arrangements, (2 folders)
        - Egypt See also Classified, (2 folders)
        - Israel
      - 1985, Oct.-Nov., Pacific Rim (Box 516)
        - Commemorative album
        - Correspondence, notes, and background material, (3 folders)
      - 1986, Oct.-Nov, Australia
        - Background material, (2 folders)
        - Billing
        - Correspondence and speeches, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 517)
        - Itineraries, (3 folders)
      - 1987, July, Israel, (2 folders)
    - Trilateral Commission
      - Correspondence, 1975-1988, undated, (4 folders)
      - Plenary meeting, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
      - Reports, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 518)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1989, undated
    - United States
      - Office of Science and Technology Policy, Advisory Committee
        - 1978, (4 folders)
        - 1979, undated, (2 folders) (Box 519)
      - Senate
        - Advisory Committee on Mutual Insurance, Judiciary Committee
          - 1978, July-1979, July, (7 folders)
          - 1979, undated, (2 folders) (Box 520)
        - Advisory Panel, Select Committee on Intelligence
          - Background material, 1988-1989, (2 folders)
          - Memoranda, statements, and reports, 1990, undated, (6 folders)
    - United States Holocaust Memorial Museum, Washington, D.C., 1987-1989 (Box 521)
    - United States-Mexico Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D.C., 1973-1974
    - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pa.
      - Advisory Board, Fels Center of Government, 1971-1974, (2 folders)
      - Board of Overseers, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1975-1981, (3 folders)
    - Washington Institute of Foreign Affairs, Washington, D.C., 1981, 1989-1990
    - Washington Star
      - Clippings, 1981
      - Correspondence
        - 1979, Jan.-1982, Mar., (4 folders)
        - 1982, Apr.-1984, July (Box 522)
      - Miscellany, 1980-1981, undated, (3 folders)
    - Wawszkiewicz, Edward J., 1987-1988, (2 folders)
    - White Burkett Miller Center, Charlottesville, Va.
      - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (2 folders)
      - George C. McGhee Global Goals Conference, 1988, (1 folder) (Box 523)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, Washington, D.C.
      - Correspondence, 1977-1990, (10 folders)
      - Inter-American Dialogue Conference, 1982, (3 folders) (Box 524)
      - Miscellany, 1978, undated, (2 folders)
    - World Future Society, 1973-1990, undated, (4 folders)
    - World hunger organizations, 1985-1988, (2 folders)
    - Xerox Corp. (Box 525)
      - Clippings, reports, and notes, 1965, 1972-1979, undated, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1972, 1987-1988, undated, (7 folders)
      - Proposed reform of antitrust laws, 1978-1979, (2 folders)
      - SCM Corp. v. Xerox Corp. (Box 526)
        - Deposition of Linowitz
          - Summary, 1974-1976, (3 folders)
          - Vols. 1-3, 1974, (3 folders)
          - Vols. 4-6, 1974, (3 folders) (Box 527)
          - Vols. 7-9, 1975, (3 folders)
          - Vols. 10-15, 1975, (6 folders) (Box 528)
          - Vol. 16, 1976 (Box 529)
        - Findings and transcripts regarding Battelle Development Corp., 1978, (2 folders)
        - Findings for Linowitz to review, 1977, (2 folders)
        - Findings regarding patent policy, 1978 (Box 530)
        - Jury instructions, 1978, (2 folders)
        - Memorandum of decision, 1978
        - Miscellany, 1974-1984, undated
        - Motions and orders, 1973-1978, (3 folders)
        - Opening statements, 1978 (Box 531)
        - Testimony by Linowitz, 1978
          - Set I, (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 532)
          - Set II, (2 folders)
        - Transcripts
          - Excerpts, 1978
            - Feb. 22, (2 folders)
            - Feb. 27, (2 folders)
          - For Linowitz to review, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 533)
      - Van Dyk Research Corp. v. Xerox Corp., 1978
      - Xerox Corp. v. Dennison Mfg. Co.
        - 1974, Apr
        - 1974, June (Box 534)
      - Xerox Corp. v. International Business Machs. Corp.
        - Amended complaint and counterclaim, 1970-1972
        - Annual reports, Xerox Corp., 1948-1960, (6 folders)
        - Background documents
          - Set I
            - 1948
            - 1949-1958, (11 folders) (Box 535)
            - 1959-1966, (3 folders) (Box 536)
          - Set II, privileged, 1949-1966, (8 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1975, undated, (2 folders) (Box 537)
        - Deposition of Linowitz
          - 1972-1973, (5 folders)
          - 1974, (2 folders) (Box 538)
        - Report and recommendations, undated
    - XXI Century Foundation, 1990-1991, (2 folders)
- Haloid Xerox, Inc., 1932-1962 (Box 538-568)
  Correspondence sent and received, organizational records, contracts, agreements, reports, printed matter, and clippings.
  - Executive management file (Box 538)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute
      - Carlson, Chester Floyd
        - Correspondence, 1947-1953, undated, (2 folders)
        - Drafts of agreements, 1944-1955
      - Certificate of incorporation, Battelle Development Corp., 1935
      - Correspondence
        - 1947, Dec.-1949, Sept., (3 folders)
        - 1949, Oct.-1953, July, (11 folders) (Box 539)
        - 1953, Aug.-1958, Dec., (13 folders) (Box 540)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1948-1958, undated, (4 folders) (Box 541)
      - Miscellany, 1947-1956, undated
      - Patent purchase by Haloid, 1949-1951, undated
      - Printed matter, 1946-1960, undated
    - Board of Directors
      - Correspondence
        - 1951-1954, (4 folders)
        - 1955-1958, (6 folders) (Box 542)
      - Minutes of meetings, 1955-1958, (4 folders)
    - Planning conferences
      - 1954
      - 1955-1958, (9 folders) (Box 543)
    - Positions held by Linowitz (Box 544)
      - Assistant to the president, 1953-1954
      - Chairman, Executive Committee, 1959-1960, undated, (2 folders)
      - Vice president, 1952-1958, (2 folders)
  - Foreign program
    - Australia
      - Correspondence, 1953-1958, (5 folders)
      - Patents by Kenneth A. Metcalfe, 1957, undated
    - Canada, 1953-1958
    - France (Box 545)
      - General correspondence, 1952-1958, (4 folders)
      - Railey, Howard B., 1957-1958
    - General correspondence, 1952-1956, (8 folders)
    - Germany (Box 546)
      - AGFA, 1955-1958, (2 folders)
      - General correspondence, 1951-1958, (6 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1954-1958
    - Great Britain
      - Ferranti Ltd.
        - 1953-1955, (3 folders)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 547)
      - General correspondence, 1952-1957, (3 folders)
      - Gestetner Ltd., 1951-1955
      - Guy's Hospital, Medical School, London, England, 1955-1958
    - Italy, 1953-1958
    - Latin America, 1954-1958